# Jakub Ożóg

# **Angular Front-End Developer / Software Engineer**

Programming became my passion during my teenage years. I began my professional journey in 2002 as a PHP developer, focusing on server-side application development. Over the next five years, I shifted my interests towards front-end technologies, creating advanced web applications and browser games using Adobe Flash. Shortly after, I discovered AngularJs, which, as it evolved into Angular, has been my constant companion to this day.

Throughout my career, I've had the opportunity to delve into a wide range of technologies, both front-end, such as FXML and WebGL, and back-end, including Java, Spring Boot, and JavaEE. For years, I've been executing projects based on the Scrum/Agile methodology, often using tools like JIRA and Confluence and collaborating with repositories on platforms like GitHub or Bitbucket. In my work, I place great emphasis on code quality, ensuring high test coverage and efficient continuous integration, managed by Jenkins.



## **Contact**

Address: Remote from Poznań in Poland

Phone: +48 667522020 E-mail: jakubozog82@gmail.com

# **Skills**

- Methodology Scrum/Agile
- Repositories GitHub/Bitbucket
- Atlassian tools JIRA/Confluence /Trello
- CI management by Jenkins/GitHub Actions/Sonar
- Unit/Integration/e2e testing
- JetBrains WebStorm/IntelliJ IDEA
- Commitment, conscientiousness and duty
- The ability to solve tasks independently
- Teamwork

# Languages

- Polish (native)
- English (C1 level)

# **Experience**

## 2023.01 -Present

# Atos SE / Eviden R&D – Senior Application Developer (Angular Developer)

- Atos is a global French corporation specializing in delivering high-performance
- computing solutions
- Work on the corporate Angular framework that unifies the appearance of internal applications
- Work on software related to AI and ML calculations.
- Technologies: Angular18, TypeScript, RxJs, NgRx, Jest, Material design, Highcharts, SonarQube, Docker, Jenkins, Jira, Confluence, Scrum

# 2021.06 - Omnigame ApS − Front-End Developer 2023-01 • Developing a website for inte

- Developing a website for internal use for data analysis based on HigHcharts in Angular.
- Creating browser games based on WebGL and PixiJS with a special focus on performance and filling experience, available on pip.dk
- Working in SCRUM philosophy
- Team work of 3 developers per game, company about 75
- Technologies as Front-End: Angular 15, TypeScript, RxJs, Material Design, Highcharts, Keycloak, Jest, Jenkins, Sonar, Bitbacket, Jira, Docker, Confluence
- Technologies as game Developer: JavaScript, WebGL, PixiJS

#### **Achievements:**

- Updating to the current version of Angular
- Learned the basic knowledge of game programming and the differences between them and application development
- Developed the taste of animation
- Work in a Danish company

## 2021.05 -2019.07

# PSI Polska Sp. z o.o. – Senior Software Engineering in R&D Framework department

- Development of a dedicated framework for internal use throughout the company. Based on a modular approach modeled on a desktop application with a predefined database structure. Focused on a generic approach
- Working with JIRA with SCRUM philosophy
- Team work of 7 people, company about 350
- Technologies: Angular 12, RxJs, TypeScript, JavaEE, PostgreSQL, Jenkins, Jira, Docker, Confluence

# **Achievements:**

- Work in the R&D department in a corporation with global range
- Being part of a highly trained and experienced team
- Coding software that is the basic work tool for other programmers
- Becoming familiar with Java EE backend approach

## 2019.06 -2016.11

# QSG S.A. – R&D Software Engineer

- Creating and maintaining desktop apps to automate the production (JavaFx, Spring Boot)
- Developing of service to manage production process (Angular)
- Working with JIRA with SCRUM philosophy
- Team work of about 6 people, company about 100
- Technologies: JavaFX, Java, Spring Boot, Maven, Angular 8, NgRx, TypeScript, Jira, Docker

# Achievements:

- Fast promotion to R&D department
- Created AR app based on ARKit 2
- Giving JavaFX courses for colleagues in team
- Working on system architecture
- Deepening knowledge about Angular

#### 2016.10 - Human2Human.technology - Front-End Developer

2017.01

- Creating a marketing tool to manage the reseller network.
- Work in a 3-person team, company about 25
- Technologies: Angular 5, TypeScript

#### **Achievements:**

• Learned Angular framework

#### 2015.11 - Neptis S.A. - Full Stack Developer

#### 2016.10

- Working on a service for real-time geo tracking of cars (JavaScript)
- Creating and maintaining service to manage cars fleet (Angular).
- Creating and developing a data service for the aforementioned project using Java,
   Spring Boot, PostgreSql
- Team work of about 6 people, company about 200
- Technologies: AngularJs, JavaScript, LeafletJs, Java, Spring Boot, PostgreSql, Maven

#### **Achievements:**

- Learned Spring Boot
- Learned Angular 1 framework

## 2010.09 - Animade Sp. z o.o. - Programmer

#### 2015.11

- Creating games and applications for browsers and mobile platforms (Android, iOS)
- Work in a 3-person team, company about 25
- Technologies: ActionScript, Flash, Android Sdk, MySql

#### **Achievements:**

- Learned Adobe technologies related to ActionScript
- Learned Android Sdk

# 2010.09 - Wide Open - Flash Developer

2008.06

- Creating RIA (rich Internet application) applications in an advertising agency
- Work in a 6-person team, company about 25
- Technologies: ActionScript, Flash, MySql

## 2008.06 - DreamLab Onet.pl Sp. Z o.o. - Programmer

2006.11

- Work in the information pages department
- Work in a 30-person team, company about 500
- Technologies: Php, MySql, JavaScript

## 2006.11 - Group Onet.pl S.A. - Programmer

2006.08

- Work in the information pages department
- Work in a 30-person team, company about 500
- Technologies: Php, MySql, JavaScript

## 2006.08 - Artyści Nowych Mediów - Programmer

2004.06

• Technologies: Php, MySql, JavaScript

2004.06 - Sof

Soft-Art – Programmer

2002.06

• Technologies: Php, MySql, JavaScript

# **Education**

Technikum Energetyczno-Elektroniczne nr 9 im. Tadeusza Kościuszki - Computer Systems

# **Trainings**

Developers Peak - Reactive Angular 4 2017r

NobleProg - Security of internet applications 2020r

NobleProg - Reactive Programming with Angular RxJS 2022r

Udemy - NestJS: The Complete Developer's Guide 2024r.

# **Interests**

I am a huge fan of music that I love to experience at various festivals. The Garbicz Festival is my favorite. I enjoy reading any of the rinpoches' literature that describes the Buddhist understanding/approach to the world. Although I am not religious myself. And of course I am a player, I like to clash with other people in the virtual world:)